<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AIRAPP-WEAR</string>

    <string-array name="title">
        <item>GOOD</item>
        <item>MODERATE</item>
        <item>UNHEALTHY FOR SENSITIVE GROUPS</item>
        <item>UNHEALTHY</item>
        <item>VERY UNHEALTHY</item>
        <item>HAZARDOUS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc">
        <item>Everyone can continue their outdoor activities normally.</item>
        <item>Only very few hypersensitive people should reduce outdoor activities.</item>
        <item>Children, seniors and individuals with respiratory or heart diseases should reduce sustained and high-intensity outdoor exercises.</item>
        <item>Children, seniors and individuals with respiratory or heart diseases should avoid sustained and high-intensity outdoor exercises. General population should moderately reduce outdoor activities.</item>
        <item>Children, seniors and individuals with heart or lung diseases should stay indoors and avoid outdoor activities. General population should reduce outdoor activities.</item>
        <item>Children, seniors and the sick should stay indoors and avoid physical exertion. General population should avoid outdoor activities.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lvl">
        <item>Air quality is considered satisfactory, and air pollution poses little or no risk.</item>
        <item>Air quality is acceptable; however, for some pollutants there may be a moderate health concern for a very small number of people who are unusually sensitive to air pollution.</item>
        <item>Members of sensitive groups may experience health effects. The general public is not likely to be affected.</item>
        <item>Everyone may begin to experience health effects; members of sensitive groups may experience more serious health effects.</item>
        <item>Health warnings of emergency conditions. The entire population is more likely to be affected.</item>
        <item>Health alert: everyone may experience more serious health effects.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
